Regent Crisostomo

Staff Pharmacist - Walmart Pharmacy

Bensalem, PA - Email me on Indeed: indeed.com/r/Regent-Crisostomo/7323bb341a40d558

A strong, comprehensive, experienced Pharmacist in Retail, Home IV Infusion, and Clinical Hospital available to acquire a position in an institution/company that can utilize my organizational skills and lead to professional growth.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Staff Pharmacist

Walmart Pharmacy - Willow Grove, PA - 2010 to Present

Traveled to various Walmart Pharmacies to manage the pharmacy and dispense prescriptions. Led technicians in proper filling and procedures. Dispensed effectively, efficiently and correctly to each patient. Proficient in using Connexus and other proprietary computer programs to fill prescriptions and manage stock. Trained in managing the pharmacy and the technicians.

Clinical Pharmacist

Kindred Hospital - Philadelphia, PA - 2009 to 2013

Led a team of pharmacy technicians to accomplish patient care in a Long Term Acute Care facility. Made medication reconciliations for new admissions. Made policy, procedures, and manual for training new pharmacist and technicians. Managed the ordering of supplies and the budget of the pharmacy. Communicated with all medical professionals in the goal of patient safety and therapy. Managed the scheduling of the pharmacists. Well trained in the Pyxis system both console and MedStation. Managed C2 inventory with ordering and physical counts. Trained all pharmacists in the ProTouch system and was a Super User. Made certain all medications leaving the pharmacy were precise and correct.

Clinical Pharmacist

Home Solutions - Horsham, PA - 2008 to 2009

Trained in IV room and USP 797 regulations. Effective leader of the pharmacy technicians and delivery drivers. Trained in communication with healthcare professionals and patients. Speak to doctors and nurses on a regular basis regarding the status and health of patients. Knowledgeable in indications, usage, dosing, and course of various IV medications. Have given clinical opinions regarding patient's treatment courses.

Staff Pharmacist

Target Pharmacy - Langhorne, PA - 2007 to 2008

Traveled to various Target Pharmacies to manage the pharmacy and dispense prescriptions. Led technicians in proper filling and procedures. Dispensed effectively, efficiently and correctly to each guest. Polite and courteous to the needs of the guest. Trained in managing the pharmacy and the technicians.

Pharmacy Technician

Target Pharmacy - Langhorne, PA - 2006 to 2007

Dispensed oral medication to Target guests. Trained in inputting prescriptions in the computer system and efficiently filling oral medication. Trained in stocking and inventory of medication from suppliers. Knowledgeable in various insurance companies and their medication coverage.

Pharmacy Technician

Abington Memorial Hospital - Abington, PA - 2003 to 2006

Delivered medication to various units in the hospital. Trained in using Pyxis machines, refilling and troubleshooting the automated filling station, drawing oral pediatric medication, medication stocking, and the IV room.

EDUCATION

PharmD

University of the Sciences in Philadelphia - Philadelphia, PA August 2001 to May 2007

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

Skills

I have had extensive training in communication with medical professionals, communication with patients, managing the pharmacy, managing the technicians, preparing IV's, dispensing medication, indications and dosage of medication, usage of various medical supplies, inputting orders in various computer programs, and line flushing protocols.